UNITE Industrial Development and Labor Management Department Records 6000/053
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Industrial Development and Labor Management Department Records
1961- 2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
6000/053
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
This collection contains a significant amount of material from ILGWU.
7130132
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 12, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications 6000/044 P: UNITE Photographs
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Fashion Institute of Technology (New York, N.Y.); Garment Industry Development Corporation; New York City Economic Development Corporation; New York State Economic Development Board; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Industrial Development/Labor Management Dept.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7130132
- ID/LM Federation for Industrial Retention & Renewal, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ID/LM Fashion Institute of technology - FIT, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- FIT Center for Design Innovation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ID/LM Garment Center, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ID/LM Garment Center Special District, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ID/LM Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ID/LM Garment Industry Domestic Revival, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ID/LM Garment Industry Research Projects (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ID/LM GIDC Activity Reports, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ID/LM GIDC Anniversary, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ID/LM GIDC Annual Report, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ID/LM GIDC Audit, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ID/LM GIDC Board Composition, 1992-2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ID/LM GIDC Board Meetings, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ID/LM GIDC Buyers' Services Program, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ID/LM GIDC Child Care Study, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- ID/LM GIDC Fashion Industry Modernization Center (FIMC), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ID/LM GIDC Marketing Program, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ID/LM GIDC NY City, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ID/LM GIDC NY State, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- ID/LM GIDC Press Coverage, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ID/LM GIDC Quality Control, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ID/LM GIDC Training, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ID/LM Harvard Center for Textile, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ID/LM ILGWU Contributions, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ID/LM ILGWU Policy Proposal, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ID/LM ILGWU Presentation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- ID/LM Industry Development Working Group, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- ID/LM Italy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- ID/LM Lady Carol, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- ID/LM Leslie Fay, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- ID/LM Lloyd Sportswear, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- ID/LM Lord West, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- ID/LM Los Angeles, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- ID/LM Made in New York, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- ID/LM Mademoiselle, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- ID/LM Marcus & Weisen, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- ID/LM Messinger's Council of Manufacturing, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- ID/LM Metropolitan Fashion Center, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- ID/LM Modular Production, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- ID/LM NIST, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- ID/LM NYC City Planning, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- ID/LM NYC Economic Development, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- ID/LM NYC Funding, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- ID/LM New York City Council, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- ID/LM New York City Workforce Development Commission, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- ID/LM NYS Economic Development, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- ID/LM NYS Funding, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- ID/LM Parrot, James, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- ID/LM Port Authority of NY & NJ, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- ID/LM Proper, Carl, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- ID/LM Quality Improvement Projects, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- ID/LM Quick Response, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- ID/LM Reich Statements, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- ID/LM Sequence International, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- ID/LM Sturz, Herbert, 1961-1990 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- ID/LM TC(squared), 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- ID/LM UNITE Industrial Development Structure, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- ID/LM Weintraub, Manny, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- ID/LM Workplace Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- ID/LM Xerox Corporation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- ID/LM Zoning (NYC), 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)